<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Home Remedies And Natural Care</string>
    <string name="rem_detail">Are you wondering what\'s the best medicine for your asthma? It depends on how severe a person’s asthma is. Everyone with asthma should have a rescue medication available, such as albuterol, for the quick relief of asthma symptoms. However, the majority of people with asthma also require a controller medication. A controller medication is used to prevent asthma symptoms and is taken every day regardless of how the person’s asthma is doing that day. First, find out if your asthma is controlled; and whether you should see your doctor so that a controller therapy (or a different controller therapy) can be prescribed. What Is the Best Medication for Asthma? Controller medicines are those medicines that are taken every day (sometimes multiple times a day) regardless of asthma symptoms. These medicines are taken all of the time in order to control the inflammation and swelling of the airways. This leads to less irritation and constriction of the muscles around the airways and therefore fewer asthma symptoms. These medicines usually take a few days to a few weeks in order to start working, but then a person with asthma notices that less and less rescue medicine is needed. Many Asthma Controllers Available These include inhaled steroids such as Flovent (fluticasone) and Pulmicort (budesonide), leukotriene blockers such as Singulair (montelukast), and combination therapy with long-acting beta-agonists such as Advair (fluticasone/salmeterol) and Symbicort (budesonide/formoterol). Other medicines, such as theophylline and Xolair, are typically used in addition to an inhaled corticosteroid or leukotriene blocker to control asthma. It would be unusual for a patient to only take theophylline or Xolair without another medicine to treat asthma.</string>
    <string name="player_error">Error initializing YouTube player: %s</string>
    <string name="seek_to">Jump To</string>
    <string name="seek_to_hint">Seconds</string>
</resources>
